http://www.biketrack.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to the content
Privacy Policy
At Bike Track, your privacy is important to us. We will not collect any personally identifying information about you unless you give us this information voluntarily. We will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third-party to use your email address or other personally identifying information for commercial purposes without your permission.
We will not send you marketing messages if you have opted out. We will not communicate to you directly via email or by phone if you have informed us that you do not wish to receive such communication. Bike Track complies with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003.
The Bike Track website uses cookies, which are small pieces of data that we place on your hard drive if you visit our website. We do not use cookies to collect any personally identifying information about you. Instead, cookies tell us about the type and version of your browser, what pages you accessed at www.BikeTrack.com and how you found us whether it be from a search engine, referral, etc. We use the information from cookies internally to compile general statistics to better administer our website and enhance the user experience. If cookies are of concern, you can modify your browser preferences. You have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is about to be set, or to disable all cookies. Consult the “Help” feature of your browser to learn more about cookies.
If you believe you have received communication from us that is not consistent with our privacy policy or if you have comments on our privacy policy, you may contact us at info@BikeTrack.com. Please specify “Privacy Policy” in the subject line.
Home
Privacy Policy
Cookie Notice
Find out more about how this website uses cookies to enhance your browsing experience.
Accept Cookies
